Preliminary Guide to the Rufus Lusk & Sons business and personal records, 1896-1994 MS2189
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Business records, 1930-1994; Series 1
  - Real estate business records, 1930-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Budget, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Baltimore Office, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Baltimore Office, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Baltimore Office, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Baltimore Office, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore Office, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Baltimore Office, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Baltimore Office lease, 1988-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Boice Dunham Group, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Bonuses, 1984-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Capital Expenses, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Cities: Atlanta, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Cities: Baltimore, 1981-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Cities: Norfolk, 1980-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Cities: Philadelphia, 1982-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Cities: Nashville, TN, 1979-1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Cities: Richmond, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - City National Bank, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - CLESA [1/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - CLESA [2/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Code calls, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Computer programs (data mail), 1979-1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Collections, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Computers: Boizelle Ins - HP, 1983-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Computers: IBM - Info Concepts [1/2], 1985-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Computers: IBM - Info Concepts [2/2], 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Computers: L & M Contracting (mailing labels) - Opus Corp., 1982-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Social Studies: Radford Financial, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Computers: Regardies' - Riggs', 1982-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Computers: Sandoz-Lamberton - Study AFL-CIO (Hemisphere NB), 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Computer study: Children's Hospital, 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Computer studies: DC Government - 1st American mgt., 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Computer study: Montgomery Co. housing opportunities commission, 1982-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Computer studies: pending - Prov. S & L, 1982-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Computer studies: Shannon & Luchs - Wilkes & Artis, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Computers: Smithy, Braedon - Joe Barrett, 1980-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Special Studies: Tenenbaum Hill - Weaver Bros., 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Computers - Tel. Costs, 1983-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Condo Directory, 1980-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Contracts [not completed form], undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Corporate Taxes, bond loss, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, RSL, III [1/3], 1988-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, RSL, III [2/3], 1981-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, RSL, III [3/3], 1978-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondants, 1988-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Cost analysis, 1974-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Dataman [1/2], 1988-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dataman [2/2], 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - DC Apartment Directory, 1980-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - DP Staff Meeting [1/2], 1988-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - DP Staff Meeting [2/2], 1988-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - DC Government Levy and Perlman [1/2], 1984-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - DC Government Levy and Perlman [2/2], 1980-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - EqFlex [flexible spending program], 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Graphs: Collections, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Graphs: Financials, 1986-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Graphs: Lusknet, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Graphs: Sales, 1985-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Guide correspondents, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - HP 3000, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - DC Statistical Booklet, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Directories, 1979-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Directory Services, 1981-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Health Plan [1/2], 1991-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Health Plan [2/2], 1985-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Heyman Mailing service, 1988-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Historical preservation, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hotel [square 372] [1/2], 1989-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Hotel [square 372] [2/2], 1989-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Housing data reports, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - I.T.A. Senior management symposium, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Insurance agency, 1985-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Inventory directories, 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Investments, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Korean Embassy, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Lamda Alpha Frat, 1983-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Lease Trend, Inc, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Leasing: cars, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Legal, 1980-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Lenders, 1987-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Levy, Nat, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Long and Foster, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Lusk new owners list, inc, 1980-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - DC - GSA, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - DC Office buildings directory sales, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - DC Office Directory, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - DC rolling fiche, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Documentation, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - EqFlex [flexible spending program], 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Everts, Arjaan, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Lusk building financial [1/2], 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Lusk building financial [2/2], 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lusknet newsletter, 1985-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Lusk on-line services, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Lusknet Ads, 1985-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Lusk leasing partners, 1983-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lusknet billing [1/3], 1985-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Lusknet billing [2/3], 1985-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Lusknet billing [3/3], 1985-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Lusknet pricing, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Lusknet "bugs", 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Lusknet DC database, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Lusknet Fairfax database, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Lusknet financial, 1986-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Lusknet Montgomery County database, 1985-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Lusknet Prince Georges County database, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Lusknet legal, 1984-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Lusknet manager functions, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Lusknet press coverage, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Lusknet seminars, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Lusknet stage III, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Lusknet system procedures, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Lusknet terminals, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Lusknet vs L2R, 1988-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Lusknet test site, 1984-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Lusknet user documentation, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Lusknet work in progress [1/2], 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Lusknet work in progress [2/2], 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Magill news, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Mgmt. meeting minutes [1/3], 1984-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Mgmt. meeting minutes [2/3], 1984-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Mgmt. meeting minutes [3/3], 1984-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Management report, 1966 February 16; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Mastercraft, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - MLS - Anne Arundel Co., 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - MLS - DC, 1982-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Maps - Alexandria, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Maps - Anne Arundel Co., 1988-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Maps - Arlington Co., 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Maps - Baltimore Co., 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Sager, Inc., 1982-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Sales [1/2], 1979-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Sales [2/2], 1979-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Sal Red Plan, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Sales - lost business, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Sedgwick, 1987-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Sept. R.E. [Real Estate] conference, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - James F. Sherry and Associates, inc., 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Sholin, Barry, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Statistics DC, 1980-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Subscribers statistics, 1957-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Surveys DC, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Survey DC, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Silver Spring office buildings, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Skelton, Bettie A., 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - SPEC print, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Special offers: Montgomery County directory, 1984 February; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Special Studies, 1981-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Special Studies: Akridge, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Special Studies: Brenneman, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Special Studies: DC LII, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Computers: Hillandale, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Special studies: Hodges, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Special studies: The Money Store, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Special studies: Mudd / Lentz, 1974-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Special study (computer): Washington Post, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - DC Project, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lusk Fall Conference, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Fall Planning Conference, 1984-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Old press releases, 1967-1971; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Productivity Award, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Profit-sharing committee [1/2], 1983-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Profit-sharing committee [2/2], 1983-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Profit-sharing investments [1/2], 1981-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Profit-sharing investments [2/2], 1981-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Promotion letters: D.C., 1983-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Promotional letters: Maryland, 1983-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Promotional letters: NOVA [northern virginia], 1983-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Property tax, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly reports, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Quotidian Press, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Real Estate Atlas, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Real Estate newsletters, 1973-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate Infonet, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Real Estate Reporter, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - REDI [1/3], 1972-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - REDI [2/3], 1972-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - REDI [3/3], 1972-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - REDI Purchase [1/2], 1987-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - REDI Purchase [2/2], 1987-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Real Estate Washington, 1980-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Retained earnings, 1977-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Roddy Report, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Survey - Montgomery County, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - FX' 87 Directory Survey, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Taxes - ITC, 1982-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Television Digest, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Television, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Telephone System, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Town and Country Realtors, 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Trade Assoc., 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - TRWS, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Unemployment taxes, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - United Appraisals, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Ward Hale Design Associates, Inc, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Washington Board of Realtors, 1980-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Washington Board of Realtors (MLS), 1981-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Washington Directory Association, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Washington R. E. Register [Real Estate Register], 1985-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - WBR Computer Conference [Washington Board of Realtors], 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - WBR - MLS - Realtron [Washington Board of Realtors], 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Weisman, 1981-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - WBR Statistics Committee [Washington Board of Realtors], 1981-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Weekly production, 1989-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Wayne E. Zeigler, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Yater medical building, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Zoning map, 1965-1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Real estate statistics, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Rufus Lusk and Sons twenty-five year anniversary, 1930-1955; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Lusk's apartment directory Montgomery County, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper articles [lusk acquired by TRW REDI], 1994 October; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Micro-fiche, 1993-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Sales meetings, 1987-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Special Studies [1/2], 1992-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Special Studies [2/2], 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Lusknet II Fall' 93 Lusk Base [1/5], 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Lusknet II Fall' 93 Lusk Base [2/5], 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Lusknet II Fall'93 Lusk Base [3/5], 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Lusknet II Fall'93 Lusk Base [4/5], 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Lusknet II Fall '93 Lusk Base [5/5], 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - scrapbook pages, 1962-1969; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Records, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Planning documents, 1992-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Promotional materials, 1985-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Lusk's Montgomery County MD apartment directory, 1957; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Press releases, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Incorporation papers, original incorporation papers amended, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate Data, Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Royalty agreement Rufus S. Lusk, Sr., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Reports sales promotion meetings, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Sales contract 1717 37th Street, NW, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Lease agreement 1824-26 Jefferson Place, NW, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Realestat, 1955 April 29; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - D.C. Recordation tax, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - S, 1941-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Sales tax, D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Sales tax, D.C., 1950-1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Social Security Act returns, 1938-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 44, Folder 24, Box R1, Folder 10)
      This file contains restrictions. See separation sheet for details.
    - Correspondence - T, 1941-1947; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Telephone answering service, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Anna L. Stuermann retirement agreement, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 3, Box R1, Folder 11)
      This entire folder is restricted for 100 years from record creation.
    - Buy-sell stock agreement, Anna L. Stuermann and Lusk Corporation, 1977-1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box R1, Folder 12, Box 45, Folder 4)
      This entire folder is restricted.
    - Correspondence - U, 1941-1950; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Arlington county index pages, 1960; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Virginia real estate directory Northern (proposed), 1954-1955; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Pranzo Di Gala menus, 1957; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Deed 1824-26 Jefferson Place, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      The documents in this folder are similar in content to the folders in boxes 43, 44, and 45.
    - Howard County Suit, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Will of Rufus S. Lusk, Jr., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Agreement Tessie M. Lusk and Rufus S. Lusk & Son, Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 3420 Dent Place, N.W. Original Purchase Agreement, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Corporation income tax, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - R, 1941-1959; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Real Estate Guide - Northern Virginia, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate Guide - Virginia, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Retailers Commercial Agency, Inc, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Rental reference service, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Twenty-Fifth anniversary party, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Thirtieth anniversary reception (Anna L. Stuermann), undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Unemployment insurance tax, 1936-1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - V, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - W, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Wylie-Smith Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Wage (prevailing) determination hearings, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Washington Guest House Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - XYZ, 1946-1947; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - D.C. Zoning map, 1958; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Zoning map, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Zoning Advisory Committee, Commissioners, D.C. [1/2], 1955-1957; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Zoning Advisory Committee, Commissioners, D.C. [2/2], 1954-1955; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Commissioners' Zoning Advisory Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Real estate directory press releases, 1948-1949; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Builders list, 1941; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Gresleigh House of M.R. Clas Onley md. Purchased summer 1941 Master Housing Agency, Arthurdale WV, not all of this is title; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - notes on buildings to be inspected, 1940; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Financial ledger pages, 1954; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - defense housing, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Clippings--real estate, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Account ledger, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      This ledger is in an oversize box.
    - Account ledger Fidelity Daily Income Trust, 1981-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - A study of Mortgage recording in Prince George's County prepared by Rufus S. Lusk and Son, Inc. Washington, DC, 1969 April - 1970 March; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Bank Account ledger, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Lusk European correspondence, 1957; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Loose pages, 1950-1956; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - [business records], 1951; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Commission folder (Rufus Lusk Jr), undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Washington Committee of National Apartment Owners Association, 1945; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 5)